Guide to the Geraldine Page Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- November 2005 Acquisition, 1865-1999
  - Personal papers, 1953-1976; 19 (Box 37)
    Includes correspondence, clippings, photographs, memorabilia, maps, postcards, travel papers, financial records, notes and printed materials by or about Geraldine Page.
  - Photographs from stage, motion picture, and television performances, and autographed photographs and related fan letters, 1950-1983; 47 (Box 38)
    Includes photographs of Page from stage productions including Absurd Person Singular, Agnes of God, and from films including Dear Heart, The Happiest Millionaire, Interiors, Pete n' Tillie, Sweet Bird of Youth, Whatever Happened to Aunt Alice, Summer and Smoke, and You're a Big Boy Now, and from television shows including Hawaii 5-0, Rod Serling's Night Gallery, HBO's The Hitchhiker. Other photographs include publicity photographs by Roy Schatt and Vivienne London; photographs of Page with Rip Torn and with others; and awards ceremony and candid backstage photographs.
  - Pencil drawing of Geraldine Page by Selene F[?], 1982 October 9 (Box 38)
  - Personal papers, 1958-1985; 19 (Box 39)
    Includes correspondence regarding The Poetry Center of 92nd Street Y, The Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, The New Dramatists Committee, and other organizations; and ticket stubs, partial scripts, household papers, and printed materials.
  - Address and phone numbers, notes, undated (Box 39)
  - Passports, 1953-1986 (Box 39)
  - Business cards, undated (Box 39)
  - Architectural blueprints for a residence, undated (Box 39)
  - Instruction manuals (Box 39)
  - Legal papers, 1982 (Box 39)
  - Financial records, 1964-1984; 13 (Box 40)
  - Clippings, 1956-1964; 10 (Box 40)
    Includes correspondence, reviews and clippings related to Geraldine Page's acting career.
  - Clippings, 1950-1967; 34 (Box 41)
  - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1953-1987; 17 (Box 42)
  - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1948-1986; 15 (Box 43)
  - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1952-1986; 14 (Box 44)
  - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1957-1992; 6 (Box 45)
  - Miscellaneous papers and clippings, 1955-1974; 5 (Box 45)
  - Acting excercises, etc., 1945-1973; 2 (Box 45)
  - Family photographs, undated (Box 45)
  - Scrapbook and related material, 1963-1965; 2 (Box 45)
  - Play and film title Index card file, undated (Box 45)
  - Absurd Person Singular, notebook, undated (Box 46)
  - Summer and Smoke, notebook, undated (Box 46)
  - Summer and Smoke, production call sheet, 1960 (Box 46)
  - The Trip to Bountiful movie booklet, printed, circa 1985 (Box 46)
  - "Captain Jack: a Tale of a Modern Pirate," by Jonathan Torn, autograph manuscript, circa 1979 (Box 46)
  - "Gertrude," notes, written in ledger, undated (Box 46)
  - Cash ledger, with loose notes, undated (Box 46)
  - Notebook, undated; 4 (Box 46)
  - Birthday book, undated (Box 46)
  - Datebooks, 1954-1959; 3 (Box 46)
  - Address books, undated; 7 (Box 46)
  - Address books, undated; 4 (Box 47)
  - Telephone number books, undated; 2 (Box 47)
  - Royal Shakespeare Company Calendar, 1981 (Box 47)
  - "Portrait of Regina," from The Little Foxes by Victor P?, painting on wood, 1968 July 12 (Box 47)
  - Small framed oil painting, undated (Box 47)
  - Scrapbook containing vintage Thanksgiving and other holiday greeting cards and postcards, circa 1908 (Box 47)
  - Vintage greeting cards, undated; 3 (Box 47)
  - Greeting cards and postcards (blank), undated; 5 (Box 47)
  - Greeting cards and postcards (blank), undated; 10 (Box 48)
  - Stationery, undated (Box 48)
  - Personalized stationery of Geraldine Page, undated; 4 (Box 48)
  - Personalized stationery of Terry Southern and Rip Torn's ship, "The Bay O' Peeg", undated (Box 48)
  - Stationery, blank envelopes, pads, and notepaper, undated; 4 (Box 49)
  - "Directory of the Bank St. School," printed material, undated (Box 49)
  - Printed material, undated; 12 (Box 49)
    Printed material consists of instruction manuals, magazines, catalogs and books
  - "The Child Stars," by Norman J. Zierold, proof, 1965 (Box 49)
  - International Thread Company sample book, color card 53, undated (Box 49)
  - "Pente, the Classic Game of Skill," game, undated (Box 49)
  - Nylon stocking product information, package cards, undated (Box 49)
  - Small picture frames, empty, undated (Box 50)
  - Table picture frame, undated (Box 50)
  - Baggage check stubs, shoulder patch, broken leather clasp, decorative billfold, undated (Box 50)
  - Locks of hair in 2 envelopes, undated (Box 50)
  - Decorative small brass plate, undated (Box 50)
  - Unidentified wooden object, undated (Box 50)
  - Stamps, business cards, notes, and loose rolodex cards, undated (Box 50)
  - Roliflex camera case, undated (Box 50)
  - Postage stamp collection, undated; 3 (Box 50)
  - Production programs from Broadway, off-Broadway, summer stock, and touring productions primarily those in which Page appeared
    - Absurd Person Singular, 1974; 4 (Box 51)
    - Agnes of God, 1974; 2 (Box 51)
    - Angela, 1969 (Box 51)
    - Blithe Spirit, 1987 (Box 51)
    - Black Comedy, 1967; 8 (Box 51)
    - Clarence, 1985 (Box 51)
    - Clothes for a Summer Hotel, 1980 (Box 51)
    - Curtain Time, 1957 (Box 51)
    - Desire Under the Elms, 1956 (Box 52)
    - The Empress, 1955 (Box 52)
    - The Great Indoors, 1966 (Box 52)
    - Hedda Gabler, 1955 (Box 52)
    - The Immoralist, 1956 (Box 52)
    - The Inheritors, undated (Box 52)
    - The Inkeeper, 1956 (Box 52)
    - The Little Foxes, 1968 (Box 52)
    - Lookaway, 1973 (Box 52)
    - Midsummer, 1953 (Box 52)
    - Mixed Couples, 1980 (Box 52)
    - Month in the Country, 1956 (Box 52)
    - Peanut Butter Sandwiches and Dreams, 1954 (Box 52)
    - P. S. I Love You, 1964 (Box 52)
    - The Rainmaker, 1955 (Box 52)
    - Separate Tables, 1957-1958; 3 (Box 52)
    - Strange Interlude, 1963 (Box 52)
    - A Streetcar Named Desire, 1974 (Box 52)
    - Sweet Bird of Youth, 1959; 3 (Box 52)
  - Stage production programs, 1950-1986; 21 (Box 53)
  - Stage production programs, heralds, and other promotional material, 1953-1981; 14 (Box 54)
  - Printed material, 1955-1992; 6 (Box 54)
    Consists of brochures, production programs, catalogs, books and magazines.
  - Photographs, 1954-1980; 6 (Box 55)
    Includes photographs of Geraldine Page, John Wayne, and others from the filming of Hondo; stage production photographs; and portraits and candid snapshots of Page, family, friends, and associates.
  - Photographs, 1942-1985; 13 (Box 56)
    Includes photographs from Page's films Beguiled, Interiors, Hondo, Honkey Tonk Freeway, The Trip to Bountiful, Summer and Smoke, Sweet Bird of Youth; stage productions Agnes of God and Sweet Bird of Youth; publicity portraits of Geraldine Page and of Rip Torn, and candid snapshots of Page with family, friends, and associates.
  - Photographs, 1950-1985; 16 (Box 57)
    Includes photographs from Page's films Interiors, The Trip to Bountiful, Summer and Smoke, Sweet Bird of Youth, The Happiest Millionaire; stage productions Agnes of God, Sweet Bird of Youth, The Top Bananna; and publicity portraits and candid snapshots of Page, family, friends and associates.
  - Clippings from the American Press Clipping Service, 1955-1978; 14 (Box 58)
  - Clippings, 1962-1968; 9 (Box 59)
  - Rip Torn memorabilia and papers, 1963-1990; 5 (Box 59)
    Includes clippings, production programs, memorabilia, and legal and financial papers pertaining to The Sanctuary Theatre Workshop, Inc.
  - Writings, notes and notebooks by Geraldine Page, 1967-1980; 12 (Box 60)
    Also includes some correspondence.
  - Personal correspondence "A" - "H", 1953-1960; 5 (Box 60)
    Includes correspondence with friends and colleagues.
  - Personal correspondence "K" - "Z", 1953-1962; 11 (Box 61)
  - Scripts
    Includes play, television and film scripts, and treatments, scenarios, etc., some of which are annotated and/or accompanied by correspondence.
    - "Absurd Person Singular," playscript by Alan Aykbourn, undated (Box 61)
    - "All the President's Men," film script by William Goldman, 1975 July 11 (Box 61)
    - "Alone," television script by Loring Mandel, undated (Box 61)
    - "Angela," playscript by Sumner Arthur Long, 1968; 3 (Box 61)
    - "Anna Christie," by Eurgene O'Neil, printed version, undated (Box 61)
    - "Arethusa," television script by Halsted Welles for Ghost Story, 1972 September 27 (Box 61)
    - "The Assassins," film script by John Stix and Gary Soulsman, undated (Box 61)
    - "Betrayed," television script by Bill Stratton produced for Medical Center, 1972 July 24 (Box 61)
    - The Biggest Thief in Town, playscript by Dalton Trumbo (New York: Dramatists Play Service), 1949 (Box 61)
    - "Black Comedy," playscript by Alexander H. Cohen, undated (Box 61)
    - "Blind Ambition," Part I, television scripts by Stanley R. Greenberg, 1978 (Box 61)
    - "Blind Ambition," Parts 2-4, television scripts by Stanley R. Greenberg, 1978; 3 (Box 62)
    - "Blues for Mr. Charlie," playscript by James Baldwin, undated (Box 62)
    - "Coma," film script by Michael Crichton, 1977 May 2 (Box 62)
    - "The Creditors: A Tragic Comedy," playscript by Palaemona Morner and R. Spacek. A modern translation based on August Strindberg, 1977 March 23 (Box 62)
    - "The Dance of Death," film script by August Strindberg, 1967 (Box 62)
    - "Death Hits the Jackpot," television script by Jeffrey Bloom, 1991 June 26 (Box 62)
    - "Dubliners," film script, draft, undated (Box 62)
    - "The Enormous Lie," playscript by Alvin Aronson, 1958 July (Box 62)
    - "Fire and Ice," television script by Richard Fielder, undated (Box 62)
    - "The First Day," film script by Roger O. Hirson, 1962 April 16 (Box 62)
    - "Flynt and Brimstone," playscript by Terry Southern, undated (Box 62)
    - "The Glass Menagerie," playscript by Tennessee Williams, undated (Box 62)
    - "Go See," playscripts by Norris Church Mailer, 1987-1989; 3 (Box 62)
    - "Hedda," playscript by Edwin Corley based on Henrik Ibsen's Hedda Gabler, undated (Box 62)
    - "The Immoralist," by Ruth and Augustus Goetz, 1944 (Box 62)
    - "In the Summerhouse," film script by Nora Johnson, undated (Box 63)
    - "The Innkeepers," playscript by Theodore Apstein, undated; 2 (Box 63)
    - "Invitation to a March," playscript by Arthur Laurents, undated (Box 63)
    - "Kingdom of Earth," playscript by Tennessee Williams, 1967 June (Box 63)
    - The Little Foxes, by Lillian Hellman (New York: Dramatists Play Service) (2 copies), 1967 (Box 63)
    - "Look Away," playscript by Jerome Kilty, annotated by Page, 1972, undated; 2 (Box 63)
    - "Look Homeward Angel," "a new musical," playscript by Gary Geld and Peter Udell, 1974 January 15 (Box 63)
    - Madwoman of Chaillot, playscript by Jean Giraudoux (New York: Dramatists Play Service) (2 copies), 1974 (Box 63)
    - "Mame," film script by Leonard Girshe, 1970 (Box 63)
    - "A Marriage Proposal" and "The Bear," television scripts by Anton Chekov, undated; 3 (Box 63)
    - "Miss Julie," playscript [by August Strindberg], "Sanctuary Theatre's translation" (Box 63)
    - "Miss Moffat," musical playscript by Albert Hague and Emlyn Williams, 1973 (Box 63)
    - "Mixed Couples," playscript by James Prideaux, 1980 May 1 (Box 63)
    - "Most Wanted: The Dutchman," television script by Stephen Kandel, 1976; 2 (Box 63)
    - "A Mother's Tale," typescipt by James Agee, 1970 (Box 63)
    - "Old Man," television script by Horton Foote for Playhouse 90, 1958 September 12 (Box 64)
    - "The Out-Of-Towners," film script by Tad Mosel, 1963 August 6; 3 (Box 64)
    - "People Are Living There," playscript by Athol Fugard, undated (Box 64)
    - "People Kill People Sometimes," television script by S. Lee Pogostin, 1959 August; 2 (Box 64)
    - "Portrait of a Murderer," television script by Leslie Stevens for Playhouse 90., 1958 February 9 (Box 64)
    - "The Rainmaker," playscript by Richard Nash, undated; 2 (Box 64)
    - "Red Dirt," film script by Terry Southern, 1977 November 22 (Box 64)
    - "Reflections in a Golden Eye," film script by Chapman Mortimer, undated (Box 64)
    - "Seduced," playscript by Sam Shepard, undated (Box 64)
    - "A Small Rebellion," television play by S. Lee Pogostin, 1965 May 28 (Box 64)
    - "Something For Joey," film script by Jerry McNeely, 1976 November 2 (Box 64)
    - "Something in the Woodwork," television script by Rod Serling from a story by R. Chetwynd-Hayes, produced for Night Gallery, 1972 June 22 (Box 64)
    - "Strange Interlude," act one, play script by Eugene O'Neil, undated (Box 64)
    - "Summer and Smoke," film script by James Poe, 1960 -1961; 2 (Box 64)
    - "Summer and Smoke," film script, 1960-1961; 3 (Box 65)
    - Summer and Smoke, playscript by Tennesee Williams (New York: Dramatists Play Service), 1950 (Box 65)
    - "Sweet Bird of Youth," playscript by Tennessee Williams, 1958, undated; 2 (Box 65)
    - "The Thanksgiving Visitor," typescript narrative and film script by Truman Capote, photocopies, undated (Box 65)
    - "This Music Crept by Me Upon the Waters," playscript by Archibald MacLeish (Box 65)
    - "Toys in the Attic," revised film script pages, 1962 October 22 (Box 65)
    - "The Trip to Bountiful," film script by Horton Foote, 1985; 2 (Box 65)
    - "Two-Character Play," playscript by Tennessee Williams, 1967 January 20; 2 (Box 65)
    - "Two for the Seesaw," playscript by William Gibson, 1956 (Box 65)
    - "Vivat! Vivat Regina!," playscript by Robert Bolt, undated (Box 65)
    - "Whatever Happened to Aunt Alice," film script, 1968 August 30 (Box 65)
    - "The White Lies," playscript by Peter Shaffer, undated; 2 (Box 65)
    - "Wire," libretto by Hayden Wayne, undated (Box 65)
    - "With Reason to Suspect," film script by Lucretia Baxter and Alan Lansburg, 1992 (Box 65)
    - Untitled Sam Shepard play, circa 1984 (Box 65)
  - Scripts, 1978 December 13
    - "The American War Mothers," playscript by Roma Greth, undated (Box 66)
    - "Anthem Street," playscript by Don Donnellan, undated (Box 66)
    - "As the Free Bird Flyeth to Heaven," playscript by Margaret Power, 1972 (Box 66)
    - "Birthday," film script by unidentified author, undated (Box 66)
    - "Cantelope, an Entertainment," playscript by Jay Zimmel, undated (Box 66)
    - "Coastline," playscript by Frank Ripley, 1962 (Box 66)
    - "Come to Glory," playscript by George Oppenheimer, undated (Box 66)
    - "Damien," playscript by Aldrich Morris, undated (Box 66)
    - "Dean," playscript by Hylan Kurneth, 1978 September 30 (Box 66)
    - "Dr. Feelgood," playscript by Alvin Aronson, undated (Box 66)
    - "The Duel," playscript by Jack Dell based on the novel by Anton Chekhov, undated (Box 66)
    - "Every Man Since Adam," typescript, 1960 (Box 66)
    - "G Flat," playscript by Alonzo Levister, undated (Box 66)
    - "Forest Burials," film script by Michael Ceraso, 1979 July (Box 66)
    - "Fit to be Tied," film script by Rudi Caringi, 1973 (Box 66)
    - "The Floor of Heaven," playscript by Frank Tuttle and Allan Gruener, undated (Box 66)
    - "High on Pilot's Bluff," playscript by Dick Hepburn, 1971 (Box 66)
    - "House of Shame," playscript by Nellise Child, undated (Box 66)
    - "House of the Blue Leaves," playscript by John Guare, 1965 (Box 66)
    - "In Dark Places," playscript by Richard Posner, undated (Box 66)
    - "The Jew Who Defended Hitler," playscript by Larry Weinberg, 1974 (Box 66)
    - "Khepera," film script by Stephen and Robert Jaffe, undated (Box 67)
    - "Lady Brimstone," film script by Lawrence Schwab, William Edwards, and Michael Plant, undated (Box 67)
    - "La Fiesta," playscript by Ernesto Fuentes, undated (Box 67)
    - "Landscape with Red Barn," playscript by Irene Kittle Kamp, 1971 (Box 67)
    - "Laurette," playscript by Stanley Young, undated (Box 67)
    - "A Little Something Before You Go," playscript by Herbert Schapiro, undated (Box 67)
    - ""Memories," film treatment by Edward Murphy, undated (Box 67)
    - "The Neon Ceilling," film script by Carol Sobieski, undated (Box 67)
    - "Nighthawks," playscript by Alvin Aronson, 1965 May (Box 67)
    - "Nineteen For Frankie," film script by Carl Methfessel and Bill Creston, 1979 (Box 67)
    - "Octette Bridge Club," playscript by P. J. Barry, 1984 (Box 67)
    - "Overtime," film script by Phillip F. Messina, 1975 (Box 67)
    - "Past Tense," playscript by Jack Zeman, 1978 December 13 (Box 67)
    - "Play with a Dead Boy," playscript by Howard Richardson, undated (Box 67)
    - "Rebel Women," playscript by Thomas Babe, 1975 (Box 67)
    - "A Safe He Can't Open," playscript by C. B. Coleman, undated (Box 67)
    - "Sailing to Byzantium," playscript by Robert Thom, 1966 (Box 67)
    - "The Savage Eye," film treatment (Box 67)
    - "Sidney and the Werewolf's Widow," playscript by Bill Manhoff, undated (Box 67)
    - "Some Men Need Help," playscript by John Ford Noonan, 1982 (Box 67)
    - "Subplot," film script by Edward Murphy, undated (Box 67)
    - "The Sudden End of Cinquefoil," playscript by Dick Hepburn, undated (Box 68)
    - "Tales of the Borderland," film script by Sidney Brammer, 1999 (Box 68)
    - "Teaser," film script, undated (Box 68)
    - "Toilers of the Sea," film script by Jay Raskin and Jan Pieter Welt, 1978 (Box 68)
    - "Touch Light," playscript by Louis C. Adelman, undated (Box 68)
    - "Turnkey," playscript by Richard W. Harris, 1978 (Box 68)
    - "When We Dead Awaken," playscript by Henrik Ibsen, undated (Box 68)
    - "Who Says There Has to be a Happy Ending," playscript by Cary Cohen, 1979 (Box 68)
    - "The Winter Soldier," playscript by Frank Mosier, 1966 (Box 68)
    - "Wolfes," film treatment by Thomas Schamoni, undated (Box 68)
    - "Works and Days," film script by Rudi Caringi, 1974 (Box 68)
    - "Woyzeck," film script by Georg Buchner, undated (Box 68)
    - Untitled scripts, revision pages, etc., undated; 5 (Box 68)
  - Correspondence
    Includes letters, notes, cards, and invitations from friends, family, and colleagues.
    - Bancroft, Ann, 1959 May 25 (Box 69)
    - Booth, Shirley, 1959 March (Box 69)
    - Bush, Barbara, 1980 December (Box 69)
    - Carlisle, Kitty (Mrs. Moss Hart), 1964 January (Box 69)
    - Crawford, Cheryl, 1960-1962 (Box 69)
    - Crawford, Joan, 1963-1965 (Box 69)
    - Disney, Walt, 1966 (Box 69)
    - Douglas, Kirk, undated (Box 69)
    - Ford, Glenn, 1963 (Box 69)
    - Harvey, Lawrence, 1960 December (Box 69)
    - Hellman, Lillian, 1955 January (Box 69)
    - Johnson, The President and Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson, 1967 (Box 69)
    - Jones, Jennifer, 1954 (Box 69)
    - Kazan, Elia, 1958-1963 (Box 69)
    - Kennedy, The President and Mrs. John F. Kennedy, 1962 April (Box 69)
    - Landau, Martin and Barbara Bain, 1956 (Box 69)
    - Lockhart, June, 1954 December (Box 69)
    - Lord, Jack, 1977 August (Box 69)
    - March, Frederick, 1959 March (Box 69)
    - Mason, Marsha, 1984 (Box 69)
    - Mastersen, Peter, 1985 February (Box 69)
    - McGavin, Darren, undated (Box 69)
    - Newman, Mr and Mrs. (Paul Newman and Joanne Woodward), 1968 January 8 (Box 69)
    - Odets, Clifford, 1952 July 11 (Box 69)
    - Papp, Joseph, 1968 (Box 69)
    - Peppard, George, 1959 March (Box 69)
    - Rigg, Diana, 1980 (Box 69)
    - Rose, Billy, 1953, 1954 (Box 69)
    - Ross, Lillian, 1963 January (Box 69)
    - Schlesinger, John, 1973 April 16 (Box 69)
    - Spacek, Sissy, 1969 December 13 (Box 69)
    - St. John, Mary, 1953 (Box 69)
    - Torn, Rip, 1957-1960 (Box 69)
    - Warhold, Andy, undated (Box 69)
      Signed form letter on Interview letterhead.
    - Wayne, John, 1967 (Box 69)
    - Williams, Tennessee, undated (Box 69)
      Floral gift enclosure cards.
    - Unsorted Correspondence, 1953-1985; 12 (Box 69)
  - Papers relating to the production of the film "The Abbess," aka Nasty Habits. including casting call sheets, script amendments, correspondence, and other material, 1976; 2 (Box 70)
  - "The Abbess," film script by Robert Enders, 1976 September; 2 (Box 70)
  - Bon voyage card inscribed with signatures, undated (Box 70)
  - Day of the Locust press Information from Paramount Pictures, 1974 (Box 70)
  - Sweet Bird of Youth promotional materials and photographs, undated (Box 70)
  - Sweet Bird of Youth contracts, casting call sheets, script pages, and photographs, 1976; 2 (Box 70)
  - "Come to Glory," playscript by George Oppenheimer, undated (Box 70)
  - "Johnny Bear," film script by Thomas Steinbeck, undated (Box 70)
  - "People Kill People Sometimes," playscript by S. Lee Pogostin, undated (Box 70)
  - "The River," film script by Robert Jiras, undated (Box 70)
  - "Splendid's," translation of playscript by Jean Genet, 1995 (Box 70)
  - "Strays," film script by Nelson Mazario, undated (Box 70)
  - "Trials of Robin Marcato," playscript by Lonnie Levister, 1987 (Box 70)
  - "The Two-Character Play," by Tennessee Williams, 1970 August (Box 70)
  - "The Umbrella," playscript by Bertrand Castelli, 1961 December 18 (Box 70)
  - Woyzeck: A Reconstruction, including playscript by George Buchner, photocopy of publication by unidentified publisher, undated (Box 70)
  - "The Dawn of Consciousness," typescript novel, annotated, undated; 2 (Box 70)
  - Handkerchief/scarf, undated (Box 71)
  - Shoes, 4 (Box 71)
  - Shoes, undated; 3 (Box 72)
  - Purple velvet cloth, undated (Box 72)
  - White bow, undated (Box 72)
  - Clippings, 1953-1982; 17 (Box 73)
    Includes loose newspaper and magazine clippings and a scrapbook pertaining to Geraldine Page's work on stage and film.
  - Printed material, 1906-1985; 17 (Box 74)
    Includes brochures, magazines, journals, catalogs and books
  - Photographs, negatives, slides, and transparencies, 11 (Box 75)
  - Framed photographs, 4 (Box 75)
  - Printed photograph of Laurette Taylor inscribed to Page, undated (Box 75)
  - Artwork by Geraldine Page and others, undated; 10 (Box 75)
    Includes pencil and ink drawing/sketches.
  - Artwork by Geraldine Page and others, undated; 14 (Box 76)
  - Cosmetic cases, memento boxes, 4 pairs of sunglasses, undated (Box 77)
  - Audiocassettes (Box 78)
    Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    Includes some audio recordings made by Page, and commercially published music. Empty cases include Rachmaninoff, Puccini, and The Police.
    - "The Trials of Robin Marcato" by Alonzo Levister, 1986 September 9; 1 (Box 78, Item barcode 39002104611810)
      Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - "Direct", undated; 1 (Box 78, Item barcode 39002104611828)
    - "Golden Memories", undated; 1 (Box 78, Item barcode 39002104611836)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 78, Item barcode 39002104611844)
    - "Great Expectations", 14, undated; 1 (Box 78, Item barcode 39002104611851)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 78, Item barcode 39002104611869)
    - "Piano music", undated; 1 (Box 78, Item barcode 39002104611877)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 78, Item barcode 39002104611885)
    - "Act II", undated; 1 (Box 78, Item barcode 39002104611893)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 78, Item barcode 39002104611901)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 78, Item barcode 39002104611919)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 78, Item barcode 39002104611927)
    - "Geraldine Page Delineation Mix", 1983 January 19; 1 (Box 78, Item barcode 39002104611935)
    - "Wire" by Hayden Wayne, undated; 1 (Box 78, Item barcode 39002104611943)
    - "Rainey Haines", Hayden Wayne, undated; 1 (Box 78, Item barcode 39002104611950)
    - "Blue Danube", undated; 1 (Box 78)
      This is a commercial audiocassette. It has not been digitized.
    - James Galway, "Mozart: The Two Flute Concertos and Andante, K. 315", 1977; 1 (Box 78)